Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 6. Executive Director, 1959-2005, 200/06
    - 3. Ann Morgan Campbell, 200/06/03
      - 4. General Files, 1959-1988, 200/06/03/04; 28.8 cubic ft. (29 boxes)
        - Series II
          - Basic Workshop Program, Reports on, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
          - Business Archives Manual, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
          - Conference on Archival Priorities, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
          - Historical Records Survey, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
          - International Congress on Archives, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
          - Manuals, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
          - Security, Miscellaneous, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18-22)
          - Ladsen, Alex, SAA Counsel, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
          - Arts and Education Bill, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
          - Copyright, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
          - Federal Budget Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
          - Federal Budget, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
          - FBI [Disposition of FBI Files], 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
          - Freedom of Information, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
          - NARA Act, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
          - NHPRC, Reauthorization of Appropriations (HR 2979), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
          - Nebraska State Historical Society Bill, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
          - Presidential Papers, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
          - Presidential Records and Documents Act, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
          - Rights to Privacy (HR 1984), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
          - Rights to Privacy Act (HR 15524), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
          - Rhode Island Public Records Bill (S815), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
          - Tax Deduction for Charitable Deductions (HR 2498), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
          - Utah State Archivist Bill (S191), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
          - London Trip, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
          - Membership Surveys, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 19-25)
          - Minnesota Manual, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 26)
          - NARS
            - Adequacy of Documentation Task Force Report, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
            - Advisory Council, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
            - Selection of Archivist of the United States, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
            - Committee on Research Use of Records, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
            - Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
            - Federal Bureau of Investigation Case, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
            - General Services Administration, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
            - Hearings Statements, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
            - Independence/Reorganization, 1975-1982 (Box 19, Folder 11)
            - Newsletter, 1980-1982, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
            - Nixon v. General Services Administration, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
            - Nixon Presidential Library, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
            - Office of Personnel Management, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
            - Oversight Committee, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
            - Miscellaneous Reports and Related Documentation, 1979-1982, undated (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
            - Presidential Libraries, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
          - North Carolina v. B. C. West, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
          - Office Space, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
          - Presidential Task Force on the Arts and Humanities, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
          - Posner's American State Archives, Supplement to, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
          - Automation, Machine-Readable Records and Archival Administration, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
          - Committees, College and University Archives Committee's Book of Readings, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
          - Machine-Readable Records Book, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
          - Manuals, Corrections and Revisions, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
          - Norton on Archives, Reprint, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
          - Publications, Church Archives, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
          - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
          - Commission on Federal Paperwork, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
          - Presidential Materials Review Board, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 13)
          - President's Administrative Services Reorganization Project, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 14-18)
          - Public Documents Commission, 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 19-22)
          - White House Conference on Libraries, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
          - White House Conference on Library and Information Services, 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
          - U.S. Senate Historian, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 25)
          - Volunteers in Archives, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 26)
          - Archival Security Project, 1975-1981 (Box 21)
          - Workshops
            - Grant Working File, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
            - Executive Director's File, 1976-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
            - United Negro College Fund Project, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
            - Basic (Phase 1), Grant Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
            - Proposal, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
            - Basic (Phase 1), General, 1977-1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
            - Basic (Phase 1), 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 7-22)
            - Architectural Records, Berkeley, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
            - Basic (Phase 2), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 2-5)
            - Business Archives, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6-9)
            - Photographs, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
            - Introduction to Archives, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
            - Appraisal and Accessioning, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
            - Arrangement and Description, 1973-1974, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
            - Conservation, 1975, 1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 15)
            - Arrangement and Description, 1973-1974, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
            - Management, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
            - Oral History, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
            - Reference and Access, 1973-1974, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
            - Security, Starting an Archives, Special Record Types, 1972, 1974, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 21)
            - Terminology-Case Study, Disc. Prob, Quiz, Outlines, Handouts, Bibliography (Box 23, Folder 22)
            - Baker Brownell Practicum (Appraisal, Arrangement & Description, Instr. Find Aid (Box 23, Folder 23)
          - Newsletters and Related Publications of Canadian and Regional Archival Organizations (Box 24)
        - Series III
          - American Archivist
            - Assignment of Rights to SAA (Article Authors), 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
            - Editorial Board, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
            - Editor Applications and Candidate Statements, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
            - Issue Editors-General Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
            - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
            - Permission to Reprint from, 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
          - Archives for Associations, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
          - Automation Bibliography (Revised), 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
          - China Trip
            - Background Material, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
            - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
            - Topical Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
          - College and University Archives Manual, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
          - Financial Records
            - Blunt, Ellis, & Loewi, Inc. (Stock Purchases), 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
            - Closed Bank Accounts, 1973-1980 (Box 25, Folder 14)
          - Grants Manual (Hackman), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 15)
          - Institutional Evaluation (Council on Library Resources Grant), 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
          - International Administration, Inc. (insurance), 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 17)
          - Lease, Printers' Square (600 S. Federal), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
          - Machine Readable Records Manual (funding), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
          - Manuals II
            - Proposal and Funding Correspondence (NHPRC), 1978-1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
            - Correspondence with Authors, 1978-1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
            - General Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
          - Membership Surveys
            - Services, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 23)
            - Programs and Activities, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 24)
            - Programs and Activities, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
          - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 26)
          - NHPRC, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 27)
          - NHPRC: Data Base, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 28)
          - National Information Systems Grant Project, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 29)
          - National Museum Act Grant (Smithsonian Institution), 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 30)
          - Overhead Projector Theft, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 31)
          - Permission to Reprint SAA Publications, 1974-1980 (Box 25, Folder 32)
          - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 33)
          - Problems in Archives Kits (PAKs), 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
          - Publications Procedures, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
          - Publications Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
          - Publications Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
          - Public Program Manual, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
          - Readership Survey, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
          - Religious Archives Bibliography, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
          - Workshops II
            - Basic Archival: Program, General, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
            - Basic Archival: Financial and Performance Grant Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
            - Business Archives, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 10-12)
            - Business Archives: Evaluation Forms, 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
            - Business Archives: Follow-up Questionnaire, 1981; Miscellaneous, 1978-1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
            - Jewish Institutions, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
          - Salary Survey, 1982 (Computer Printout)
            - Descriptive Statistics without Salaries (Entire Respondent Group) (Box 27, Folder 1)
            - Descriptive Cross Tabulations without Salaries (Entire Respondent Group) (Box 27, Folder 2)
            - Descriptive Statistics with Salaries (Entire Respondent Group) (Box 27, Folder 3)
            - Breakdowns for Full-Time Employed Respondents by Salary (Box 27, Folder 4)
            - Breakdowns for Full-Time Employees (Total Income) (Box 27, Folder 5)
          - Accountant, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
          - Accreditation/Certification, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 2)
          - American Society of Association Executives Group Insurance Trust Office, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 3)
          - American National Standards Institute, 1984-85 (Box 28, Folder 4)
          - AMIGOS, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
          - Anvan/Printers Square, 1983-88 (Box 28, Folder 6)
          - Associations
            - AAM, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 7)
            - AASLH, 1982-87 (Box 28, Folder 8)
            - AHA, 1983-85 (Box 28, Folder 9)
            - ALA, 1982-87 (Box 28, Folder 10)
            - American Society for Information Science, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
            - American Society of Association Executives (Box 28, Folder 12)
            - ARMA, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
            - Association of Research Libraries, 1983-87 (Box 28, Folder 14)
            - Catholic Library Association, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 15)
            - Coalition to Save our Documentary Heritage, 1982-84 (Box 28, Folder 16)
            - Committee on Records of Government, 1984-85 (Box 28, Folder 17)
            - Council of National Library and Information Associations, 1982-86 (Box 28, Folder 18)
            - Council on Library Resources,1986-87 (Box 28, Folder 19)
            - Council on Public History, 1980-87 (Box 28, Folder 20)
            - ICA, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21-22)
            - Institute of Certified Records Managers, 1982-85 (Box 28, Folder 23)
            - International Institute of Municipal Clerks, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 24)
            - National Association of State Archivists and Records Administrators, 1983-85 (Box 28, Folder 25)
            - NAGARA, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 26)
            - National Commission on Library and Information Science, 1983-86 (Box 28, Folder 27)
            - National Conservation Advisory Council, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 28)
            - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 29-31)
            - National Council on Public History, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 32)
            - National Historical Publications and Records Commission, 1982-85 (Box 28, Folder 33)
            - National Humanities Alliance, 1984-87 (Box 28, Folder 34)
            - National Information Center for Local Government Records, 1985-87 (Box 28, Folder 35)
            - OAH, 1984-85 (Box 28, Folder 36)
            - Society for History in the Federal Government, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 37)
            - Special Libraries Association, 1983-86 (Box 28, Folder 38)
            - Western Conservation Congress, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 39)
          - Automated Archival Information Program Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - Babbage Institute, Charles, 1983-85 (Box 29, Folder 2)
          - Certification Poll, 1986-87 (Box 29, Folder 4)
          - China Trip, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
          - China Trip-Participants, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
          - Chinese Archival Delegation Project, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
          - Chinese Archival Exchange, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 8)
          - Clippings, 1974-1985 (Box 29, Folder 9-11)
          - Coker Estate, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 12)
          - Colonial Dames of America, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
          - Computer Conversion, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
          - Dun and Bradstreet Report, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 15)
          - Executive Director Search, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
          - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 17)
          - Four-H Center,1984; Council and Goals and Priorities Task Force Meetings (Box 29, Folder 18)
          - Freedom of Information Act, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 19)
          - General Services Administration, 1982-1983; National Archives and Records Service (Box 29, Folder 20)
          - General Services Administration, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 21)
          - Grants
            - Congressional Papers 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 22)
            - Constitution-We the People, Americans and Their Constitutions, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 23)
            - Proposal Ideas, 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 24)
            - National Museum Act, 1984 Application and Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 25)
            - Senators' Papers, Proposed, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 26)
          - Holidays, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 27)
          - Illinois Bell, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 28)
          - Illinois Division of Employment Security, 1985 Fraudulent Claim (Box 29, Folder 29)
          - Insurance Center Building, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 30)
          - International Business Machines, 1972-1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
          - Lawyers Guild vs Attorney General of the United States, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 32)
          - Library of Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 33)
          - Management Newsletter, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 34)
          - Marshall Library, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 35)
          - Membership Statistics, 1974-1984 (Box 29, Folder 36)
          - Member Survey
            - Priorities for the Future (Box 29, Folder 37)
            - Value of Services (Box 29, Folder 38)
          - National Archives and Records Administration Agresto, John, 1988 Nomination to be Archivist of US (Box 29, Folder 39)
          - National Archives and Records Administration (Service) Archivist of the US (Box 29, Folder 40)
          - National Archives and Records Administration (Service) Correspondence, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 41)
          - NARA/NARS Independence Legislation Correspondence, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
          - NARA/NARS Records Declassification Task Force, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
          - NARA/NARS Smithsonian Report, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
          - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
          - Norton, Margaret Cross, Bequest, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
          - Nuclear Freeze, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 6)
          - Office of Personnel Management, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
          - Ownership, Statement of, 1968-74 (Box 30, Folder 8)
          - Pandolfi, Topolski, Weiss and Associates, 1984-1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
          - Presidential Materials Review Board, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
          - Public Archives of Canada, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 24)
          - Regionals
            - Mailings Lists 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 25)
            - Alabama Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 26)
            - Australian Soc. of Archivists 1983 (Box 30, Folder 27)
            - California Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 29)
            - Canadian Archivists, Assoc. of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 30)
            - Chicago Area Archivists 1984 (Box 30, Folder 31)
            - Colorado Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 32)
            - England, Society of Archivists 1983 (Box 30, Folder 33)
            - Florida Archivists, Society of 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 34)
            - Georgia Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 35)
            - Kentucky Council on Archives 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 36)
            - Long Island Archives Conference 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 37)
            - Michigan Archival Association 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 38)
            - Mid-Atlantic Reg. Archives Conference. 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 39)
            - Midwest Archives Conference 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 40)
            - Mississippi Archivists, Soc. of 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 41)
            - New England Archivists 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 42)
            - New York Archivists Roundtable 1983 (Box 30, Folder 43)
            - Northwest Archivists 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 44)
            - Ohio Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 45)
            - Southwest Archivists, Society of 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 46)
            - Tennessee Archivists 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 47)
          - Request for Proposal In-house Computer System, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
          - SAA History, 1936-1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
          - Salary Survey, 1982-1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
          - Schwarz Paper Company, 1979-1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
          - State Archives (Miscellaneous), 1982Administrative Reorganization (Box 31, Folder 5)
          - Study Tour, 1985 Annual Meeting (Box 31, Folder 6)
          - Sunset Laws, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
          - Tinker Foundation, 1975-76 (Box 31, Folder 8)
          - UNESCO, General Information Program, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
          - White House Conference on Library and Information Services, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - 5. Annual Meetings, 1974-1986, 200/06/03/05; 7.4 cubic ft. (7 boxes)
        - Local Arrangements, 1974
          - Advertisements and Exhibits (Box 1, Folder 1)
          - Contracts (Box 1, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
          - Finance (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - General (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - Hotel Relations (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Kodak Breakfast (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Letters of Appreciation (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - Program (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - Registration (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - Program Committee, 1974
          - 1973 June-1974 October (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
          - Documents (Box 1, Folder 14)
          - Local Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 15)
          - Reactions (Box 1, Folder 16)
          - Session Planning Working Papers (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - Session Reports (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Local Arrangements, 1975
          - General (Box 1, Folder 19)
          - Union League, Responses to Proposed Meeting At (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Local Arrangements, 1976
          - Backup Material (Box 1, Folder 21)
          - Exhibits (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - Fiscal (Box 1, Folder 23)
          - General (Box 1, Folder 24)
          - Hotel Selection (Box 1, Folder 25)
          - International Council on Archives Program (Box 1, Folder 26)
          - Local Tours (Box 1, Folder 27)
          - Minutes and Reports (Box 1, Folder 28)
          - Physical Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 29)
          - Registration (Box 1, Folder 30)
          - Travel Coordinators (Box 1, Folder 31)
          - SAA Meeting in Washington, D.C., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Program Committee, 1975
          - Members, Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Communications with Committee by Chair (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - McCree, Mary Lynn (Chair)-Sessions and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - Daniels, Maygene (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Donovan, Lynn (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Elliott, Tom (Box 2, Folder 6)
          - Fleckner, John (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - Gordon, Robert (Box 2, Folder 8)
          - Hackman, Larry (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Henn, Jim (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - Kinney, John (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Lothyan, Phillip (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Papenfuse, Edward (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Pederson, Ann (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Weldon, Ed (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Williams, Richmond (Box 2, Folder 16)
          - Wilson, Ian (Box 2, Folder 17)
          - Local Arrangements Liaison (Box 2, Folder 18)
          - Meeting-1975 January, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
          - Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference (Box 2, Folder 20)
          - Program Improvements Suggested (Box 2, Folder 21)
          - Printed Program (Correspondence, Rough Drafts, and Proofs) (Box 2, Folder 22)
          - Program Suggestions (Box 2, Folder 23)
          - Program Suggestions, Correspondence Regarding (Box 2, Folder 24)
          - Report on Sessions (Box 2, Folder 25)
          - Session and Workshop Guidelines (Box 2, Folder 26)
          - Session Responsibilities (Box 2, Folder 27)
          - Session Worksheets (Box 2, Folder 28)
          - Thank You Letters (Box 2, Folder 29)
          - Theme (Box 2, Folder 30)
          - Workshop-"Conservation of Paper Documents" (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - Local Arrangements, 1977
          - General (Box 2, Folder 32)
          - Carter, President Jimmy's Letter to the 41st Annual Meeting, 1977 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 33)
          - Travel Coordinators (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - Program Committee, 1978
          - Papenfuse, Edward C.-Chairperson (Box 2, Folder 35)
          - Printed Program Drafts (Box 2, Folder 36)
          - Worksheets (Box 2, Folder 37)
        - Local Arrangements, 1978
          - Annual Meeting Suggestion and Evaluation Form (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Deposits (Box 3, Folder 2)
          - Hughes, Cleo A.-Chairperson (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - Hyatt Regency Hotel (Box 3, Folder 4)
          - General (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Registration Lists (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Local Arrangements, 1979